

EMRE ÇOBAN

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE ENGINEERING STUDENT



emre02onur09@gmail.com



+90 542 844 06 02



Emre Çoban



b2200765028



emre02onur09

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python

Libraries: Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-Learn, Seaborn, Matplotlib, OpenCV , PyTorch ,TensorFlow

- SQL
- Java
- C++

LANGUAGES

TURKISH

Professional Working Proficiency - Primitive Language

ENGLISH

Professional Working Proficiency

Hardworking and enthusiastic College Student working towards a B.S in Artificial Intelligence Engineering. Junior year student at Hacettepe University with 3.46/4.00 Gpa. I like to study and research new things.Interested in deep learning and computer vision especially. Also studying Reinforcement Learning nowadays.



EDUCATION

2016-2020

Etimesgut Anatolian High School

GPA: 91.94 / 100.00

2020-Present

Hacettepe University, Department of Computer Science

Artificial Intelligence Engineering - Junior Year Student

GPA: 3.46/4.00



EXPERIENCE

June 2022-August 2022 Sisasoft Bilgi Teknolojileri ve İnovasyon A.Ş.

Al Engineering Intern

Worked on Deep Learning especially in Computer Vision with Al Team

November 2022-Present

Turkish Aerospace Industries (TUSAS)

Al Engineering Intern

Working as Sky Experience Intern with AI Team.



PROJECTS

Bank Marketing Project

This is an Data Mining project based upon a binary classification problem which I developed for Project of AIN429 Lecture. Dataset taken from the "data.world" and contains banking data includes information of customers such marital status, education etc. I used Data Science techniques to evaluate and inspect data and created ML models and compared them

Generate Questions with Custom Data

This is an NLP Project aiming to generate a question given a context. Me and my friend created this project for AIN311(Machine Learning) Final Project. We used T5 base model and fine-tuned it. Our model has 2 steps first it generates possible answers with the help of keywords extraction then it generates questions with given answers using attention mechanism.